<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:weightSum="3"
    tools:context="com.example.android.popularmovies.DetailActivityFragment">

    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_weight="2">

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/backdrop"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:background="#cccccc" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/original_title"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:text="Original Title"
            android:textColor="#fff"
            android:textSize="28sp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />
    </RelativeLayout>

    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="fill_parent"
        android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
        android:layout_weight="1"
        android:paddingTop="4dp">

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/poster"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="#000" />

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginLeft="24dp"
            android:layout_toRightOf="@id/poster"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/release_date"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Release Date"
                android:textSize="20sp" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/rating"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="x/10 by y users"
                android:textSize="16sp" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/overview"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
                android:scrollbars="vertical"
                android:text="Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola. Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs beef ribs turducken ball tip, jowl meatball pork belly bresaola venison pork chuck picanha tongue swine. Cupim fatback cow pancetta flank, chuck spare ribs ground round leberkas ham hock venison. Bacon short loin shankle prosciutto landjaeger, ribeye t-bone fatback flank boudin corned beef shoulder. Capicola short loin jowl, salami hamburger kevin shoulder ribeye boudin bresaola."
                android:textSize="16dp" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </RelativeLayout>
</LinearLayout>
